(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ワールドワイドな
World-wide...
最強アイドル！
Strongest idol!
それが
That is...
最強アイドル はあちゃまっちゃま
Strongest idol, Haachama-chama
どうも、赤井はあとです。
Hello, I'm Akai Haato.
今日は私、はあちゃまの誕生日。記念すべき今日という日に来てくれて感謝する。
Today is my, Haachama's, birthday. I'm grateful you came on this memorable day.
ハッシュタグは「#はあちゃま爆誕祭2024」で拡散よろしく。
The hashtag is #HaachamaBakutansai2024. Please spread the word.
私は一つ、大きな計画がある。
I have one big plan.
それは、「万物に愛されちゃま計画」だ。
That is the "Plan to be Loved by All Things."
ありとあらゆる万物に愛されるというライブ。
A live show to be loved by each and every thing.
表向きはね。
That's just the official story.
本当は、B-A-Nのブツ...
Actually, it's about B-A-N's things...
BANブツに愛されるためのライブ。
A live show to be loved by BAN-butsu.
隙を見せて、BANギリギリを攻めていこうと思う。
I'll show some openings and push the boundaries of being banned.
闇のはあちゃま勢力よ、今、立ち上がれ！
Dark Haachama forces, rise up now!
はあちゃま様ー、そろそろ誕生日ライブのお時間ですよー。
Haachama-sama, it's almost time for your birthday live.
はーい！今すぐ行きまーす！
Yes! I'm coming right now!
うぅ〜！一丁暴れ取りますか！
Nngh! Let's go wild!
チート、gifted、あ、俺はwas wanted
Cheat, gifted, ah, I was wanted
禁忌、禁じ手、明らかモン太
Forbidden, taboo move, clearly Monta
反則、異次元、この世のものではないです
Foul, another dimension, not of this world
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないて
Impossible game, I didn't sign up for that
Ay、ライバル、口を揃えて
Ay, rivals all say in unison
Wow、ライバル、口を揃えて
Wow, rivals all say in unison
バグで、まぐれ、認めねーゼッテー
A bug, a fluke, I'll never admit it
マジで？コレおま全部生身で？
Seriously? You're doing all this raw?
It's 生身、It's 生身
It's raw, it's raw
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang
Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
実力を発揮し切る前に
Before I even show my full potential
相手の方がバテてくらしい
It seems my opponent gets exhausted
上がり切るハードル very happy
Rising hurdles, very happy
あきらかにダントツでエグい
Clearly, uniquely insane
相変わらず脱皮してるまに
While I keep molting as usual
Bling, Bling
誰の七光もいらない
Don't need anyone's reflected glory
お前のiceよりicy
Icier than your ice
俺、パッと見出来損ない事ばかりだけど
I might look like a failure at first glance
very happy
あ、キレてる...呆れてる周り
Ah, snapping... People around me are shocked
恵まれてる家族友達 happy
Blessed with family and friends, happy
もう反則的立ち位置
A position that's almost cheating
皆に任せときゃ良い
Just leave it all to everyone
教科書に無い、問題も無い
Not in textbooks, no problem
超badなまじない listen
A super bad spell, listen
鏡よ鏡、答えちゃって
Mirror mirror, go ahead and answer
Who's the best? I'm the best!
Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで
Going as far as I can while being raw
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで
Eyday, just being myself
超 Flex
Super Flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, no one can butt in
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで
Eyday, just being myself
超 Flex
Super Flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟ませない
Eyday, I won't let anyone butt in
yeah yeah yeah、学歴も無い
yeah yeah yeah, no academic background
前科も無い、余裕で Bling-Bling
No criminal record, easy bling bling
この存在自体が文化財な脳味噌
This existence itself is a cultural asset of a brain
Bling-Bling
高級車は買える免許は無い
Can buy luxury cars, don't have a license
愛車 Green-Green
Favorite car is green green
全国各地揺らす逸品
A masterpiece that shakes the whole country
このベロが Bling-Bling
This tongue is bling bling
バレットなら満タン
Full of bullets
関西訛り、生身のコトダマ
Kansai accent, raw spirit
音楽、幸運、勝利の女神
Music, luck, the goddess of victory
今宵も三馬当番
Three-stage fire tonight
漫画みたいな輩とまんまで
With ruffians straight out of a manga
張り合えてしまってる漫画
A manga where they end up competing
圧倒的チカラとか
Overwhelming power and such
この頭と口から
From this head and mouth
この身体 tattooは入ってない
No tattoos on this body
このズラに傷もついてない
No scars on this face
繰り返しやらかしてくダメージ
Repeating mistakes and taking damage
繰り返しやらかしてダメージが
Making mistakes over and over, the damage...
イカつい年輪を刻み皺
...carving out tough growth rings and wrinkles.
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
俺のままで Blingして Bangして 番するまで Bornして来た
Remaining as I am, Bling-ing, Bang-ing, I was Born to wait for my turn.
鏡よ鏡 答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, give me an answer.
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah!
生身のまま 行けるとこまで
Just as I am, as far as I can go.
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top.
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top.
Eyday 俺のままで 居るだけで 超 Flex
Everyday, just being myself is a huge Flex.
Eyday 誰も口を 挟めない (won't stop)
Everyday, no one can interrupt (won't stop).
Eyday 俺のままで 居るだけで 超 Flex
Everyday, just being myself is a huge Flex.
Eyday 誰も口を 挟ませない (Don't test)
Everyday, I won't let anyone interrupt (Don't test).
はあちゃまさん、まだですか？
Haachama-san, aren't you ready yet?
もうライブ始まっちゃいますよ。
The live concert is about to start.
ほら、ほら、始まっちゃいます。
Look, look, it's starting!
ほらほら、早く、急いで、急いで！
Come on, come on, hurry, hurry!
もう、皆さんも待ってますから！
Everyone is already waiting!
早く早く！
Hurry, hurry!
はーい、おきまるー！
Okaay, roger that!
よし。準備運動も完了したことだし、
Alright. Now that the warm-up is done,
まずは、あらゆるもの、万物に愛されていこう。
first, let's go be loved by everything, by all of creation.
まずは子供たち。小さい頃から英才教育。
First, the children. Gifted education from a young age.
次はオタク。激カワきゅんきゅんをお届けしよう。
Next, the otakus. I'll deliver some super cute kyun-kyuns.
次はカップルチャンネルが好きそうに、ときめきを伝える。
Next, I'll convey some heart-fluttering moments, like a couple channel would love.
そして、ガールズクラッシュ。
And then, girls' crush.
同性にもぶっ刺さる、憧れになるかっこいい女性を目指す。
I'll aim to be a cool woman that even the same gender admires.
魅力、増し増ししていっちゃおうかな？
Maybe I'll increase my charm even more?
ストリート、ヒップホップ。
Street, hip-hop.
かっこいいバトルで、イケメンな一面も見せよう。
I'll show a cool side of myself through an awesome battle.
そして最後は、海外に向けたEnglish。
And finally, English for overseas.
頑張ります。
I'll do my best.
ざっとこんな感じだろう。
That should about cover it.
さては、計画開始！
Well then, start the plan!
妖怪体操第一！
Yokai Taiso Dai-ichi!
ウィッス！
Wissu!
ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる 妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Yo-deru, Yo-deru, Yo-deru, Yo-deru, because a Yokai appears, I can't leave.
ローイレ ローイレ 仲間にローイレ 友達大事
Ro-ire, Ro-ire, let me join, friends are important.
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Yokai, Yokai, Yokai, Watch-chi!
カイカイ キキキ クイクイ ケケケ コーイコーイ 妖怪ウォッチッチ！
Kai-kai, Ki-ki-ki, Kui-kui, Ke-ke-ke, Koi-koi, Yokai Watch-chi!
今日は朝から 寝坊した
I overslept this morning.
夢の中では 起きたのに
Even though I woke up in my dream.
どうして朝は 眠いんだ？
Why am I so sleepy in the morning?
ドゥワーッハッハー！
Do-wah ha ha!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね
It's because of a Yokai, isn't it? Yes, it is.
ウォッチ！今何時？
Watch! What time is it?
一大事ー！
A major crisis!
ウィッス！
Wissu!
ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる 妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Yo-deru, Yo-deru, Yo-deru, Yo-deru, because a Yokai appears, I can't leave.
ローイレ ローイレ 仲間にローイレ 友達大事
Ro-ire, Ro-ire, let me join, friends are important.
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Yokai, Yokai, Yokai, Watch-chi!
カイカイ キキキ クイクイ ケケケ コーイコーイ 妖怪ウォッチッチ！
Kai-kai, Ki-ki-ki, Kui-kui, Ke-ke-ke, Koi-koi, Yokai Watch-chi!
どうしてあの子に 振られたの？
Why did that girl dump me?
こんなにイケメン なのに
Even though I'm so handsome.
どうして僕ちゃん 振られたの？
Why did I get dumped?
ドゥワーッハッハー！
Do-wah ha ha!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね
It's because of a Yokai, isn't it? Yes, it is.
ウォッチ！今何時？
Watch! What time is it?
フライングマシーン！
Flying machine!
ウィッス！
Wissu!
ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる 妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Yo-deru, Yo-deru, Yo-deru, Yo-deru, because a Yokai appears, I can't leave.
ローイレ ローイレ 仲間にローイレ 友達大事
Ro-ire, Ro-ire, let me join, friends are important.
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Yokai, Yokai, Yokai, Watch-chi!
カイカイ キキキ クイクイ ケケケ コーイコーイ 妖怪ウォッチッチ！
Kai-kai, Ki-ki-ki, Kui-kui, Ke-ke-ke, Koi-koi, Yokai Watch-chi!
今日はピーマン 食べられた
I was able to eat bell peppers today.
いつもは絶対 残すのに
Even though I always leave them.
どうしてピーマン 食べられた？
Why was I able to eat bell peppers?
ドゥワーッハッハー！
Do-wah ha ha!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね
It's because of a Yokai, isn't it? Yes, it is.
ウォッチ！今何時？
Watch! What time is it?
イケるぜ この味ー！
I can do it, this taste!
ウィッス！
Wissu!
ようかい体操第一
Yo-kai Exercise No. 1
もういっちょ！
One more time!
いってみようかい？
Shall we go... kai?
どうしてうんちはくさいんだ？
Why does poop smell?
食べたものはくさくない。
The food I ate didn't smell.
どうしてうんちはくさいんだ？
Why does poop smell?
食べたものはくさくない。
The food I ate didn't smell.
どうしてうんちはプンプンプン？
Why does poop smell so bad?
どうしてうんこはプンプンプン？
Why does poo-poo smell so bad?
ドワハッハ！
Dwahahaha!
ヨーカイのせいなのね
It's because of a Yo-kai
そうなのね
That's why
ウォッチ！今何時？
Watch! What time is it now?
クショータイム！
Poop-show time!
ウィッス！
Whiss!
ヨーデリ ヨーデリ
Yodely yodely
妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Yo-kai come out, so I can't come out
ローイレ ローイレ
Join in, join in
仲間にローイレ
Join our group
友達大事
Friends are important
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Yo-kai, Yo-kai, Yo-kai, Watchitchi!
カイカイ キイキイ クイクイ ケイケイ
Kai-kai, Kii-kii, Kui-kui, Kei-kei
コイコイ 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Koi-koi, Yo-kai, Watchitchi!
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
スイートマジック
Sweet Magic
甘くて幸せなコト
Sweet and happy things
隠し味何にしよう
What should I use for the secret ingredient?
純粋な乙女心
A pure maiden's heart
甘い恋絡めなくちゃ
Must entwine it with sweet love
本気さ重ねてみるよ
I'll try layering on my sincerity
酸味も積み上げると
And if I pile up the sourness too
苦味もチョコレートケーキ
Even the bitterness becomes a chocolate cake
魔法をかけた 甘い奇跡
A sweet miracle cast with magic
甘さを抑えてビターとか
Maybe a bit bitter by holding back the sweetness
ミルク無しのコーヒーとか
Or coffee without milk
おませなフリして大人になれないの
I can't become an adult by just acting mature
そんなの絶対絶対やだやだ
I absolutely, absolutely hate that
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
ねえ！あげようか
Hey! Shall I give it to you?
甘い罠
A sweet trap
ほら虜にしてあげる
Look, I'll make you a captive
そんな魔法 かけるから
Since I'm casting that magic
ちょっとだけ待たせちゃうわ
I'll make you wait just a little bit
スイーティ スイーティ スイートマジックな
Sweety, sweety, sweet magic
スイーティ スイーティ スイートイェイイェイ
Sweety, sweety, sweet yay yay
スイーティ スイーティ スイートマジックな
Sweety, sweety, sweet magic
スイーティ スイーティ
Sweety, sweety
たったひとくちが足りなくて
Just one bite isn't enough
赤いイチゴみたく意地張って
Stubborn like a red strawberry
不満な顔なんて見せないわ
I won't show a dissatisfied face
完璧に作るもん 一人ででもでもでも
I'll make it perfectly, even all by myself
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
ねえ！気付いてんでしょ？
Hey! You've noticed, haven't you?
わかってんでしょ？
You understand, right?
隠し味の恋心
The secret ingredient of love
苦味とか 酸味とか
Bitterness, sourness...
そういうのもたまにはいいわ
Things like that are fine once in a while
意地っ張りで わがままな
A stubborn and selfish
そんな甘い魔法使い
Sweet little witch
Wow wow...
輝いたのは鏡でも太陽でもなくて
It wasn't a mirror or the sun that shone...
君だと気付いた時から
...but when I realized it was you.
あの涙ぐむ雲のずっと上には
Far above those tearful clouds...
微笑む月
...is the smiling moon.
Love story また一つ
Another love story...
傷ついた夢は昨日の彼方へ
Broken dreams fade into yesterday's distance.
空に響け愛の歌
Let the song of love echo in the sky.
想い出ずっとずっと忘れない空
Memories in a sky I'll never ever forget.
二人が離れていっても
Even if the two of us drift apart.
こんな好きな人に出会う季節二度とない
There will never be another season
where I meet someone I love this much.
光ってもっと最高のLady
Shine even more, the best Lady.
きっとそっと想い届く
Surely, softly, these feelings will reach you.
信じることがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything. Love so sweet.
Wow wow...
そこからいつも見えるように
So that it can always be seen from there...
この手を空に向け
I'll point my hand toward the sky.
広がる君との思い出
Memories of you spread out.
あの頑なで意地っ張りな僕を
The stubborn and obstinate me...
変えた君の手
...was changed by your hand.
Love story 歩き出す
A love story begins to walk.
曲がりくねってた二つの旅路は
The two winding journeys...
ここで一つ虹になれ
...shall become one rainbow here.
想い出ずっとずっと追いかけた夢
Memories of a dream chased for so, so long.
二人が遠くへ行っても
Even if the two of us go far away.
どんな辛い夜も挫けそうな誓いでも
No matter how painful the night,
or how fragile the vow...
笑ってもっと最高のLady
Smile even more, the best Lady.
きっとそっと願い届く
Surely, softly, the wish will reach.
明けない夜はないよ Love so sweet
There is no night that doesn't end. Love so sweet.
伝えきれぬ愛おしさは
This loveliness that cannot be fully expressed...
花になって街に降って
...becomes flowers and falls upon the town.
どこにいても君をここに感じてる
No matter where I am, I feel you here.
想い出ずっとずっと忘れない空
Memories in a sky I'll never ever forget.
二人が離れていっても
Even if the two of us drift apart.
こんな好きな人に出会う季節二度とない
There will never be another season
where I meet someone I love this much.
光ってもっと最高のLady
Shine even more, the best Lady.
きっとそっと想い届く
Surely, softly, these feelings will reach you.
信じることがすべて
Believing is everything.
明けない夜はないよ
There is no night that doesn't end.
信じることがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything. Love so sweet.
Wow wow...
美人
Beautiful Person
Ha!
Ah!
Uh...
Ah...
Ah, ah, yeah...
Chura chura chu- in
愛の信者はO.I.N.
Devotees of love are O.I.N.
己は平安スタイルで
I go with Heian style
べたべたべた... 見えるのに
Sticky, sticky, sticky... I can see it
助けて
Help me
私も貴方様みたいになりたい
I want to be just like you
教えて教えて 幸せでしょうね
Tell me, tell me, you must be happy
もしこのまま消えたら 愛されるのなら
If I disappear like this, and if I were loved
今すぐにでも綺麗になくなりたい
I want to fade away beautifully right now
なんで はずないわよ べっぴん
Why? No way, beauty
もう少しだけ べっぴん べっぴんに
Just a little more, beauty, beauty
コントラストも入れて頂戴
Give me some contrast too
全世界を凝らしめたい
I want to punish the whole world
Look at this
Look at this 悲しかも e-e-e
Look at this, maybe it's sad, e-e-e
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a little more glow
女盛り舐めたら や-わ-や
Don't underestimate a woman in her prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい
Was there a goddess in the toilet?
おったんなら捕まえなさい
If she was there, catch her
ちゃみなさい マジ可愛い
Look at me, I'm seriously cute
私は忘れないあの嵐
I won't forget that storm
あの時私はまだセブンティーン
Back then, I was still seventeen
あの時言ってよね 言ってよね
You should have said it then, right?
You can be beautiful, you can be famous
醜いブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
An ugly hag isn't the one singing
あの時狂った青春に才能が開花
Talent bloomed in those crazy youth days
味わったことも言ったんじゃなかった？
Didn't I say I'd experienced it too?
物置君は知ってるかい
Do you know, storage boy?
知識と経験のエロス
The eros of knowledge and experience
まだ使い物になってるかい
Are you still useful?
女は皆正気じゃない
Women are all insane
I AM BEAUTIFUL!
Look at this
Ah, look at this
Look at this, look at this, look at this!
Look at this 悲しかも e-e-e
Look at this, maybe it's sad, e-e-e
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a little more glow
女盛り舐めたら や-わ-や
Don't underestimate a woman in her prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい
Was there a goddess in the toilet?
おったんなら捕まえなさい
If she was there, catch her
Can you hear me? I'm beauty
Stay like you are, f**king beauty
予想外 驚きなさい
Be surprised by the unexpected
磨いたらダイヤ 美しい
When polished, it's a diamond, beautiful
時間的 いや 美学的
Temporal, no, aesthetic
磨いたらダイヤ 美しい
When polished, it's a diamond, beautiful
生きなさい 今見せなさい
Live your life, show it now
貴方こそダイヤ 美しい
You are the diamond, beautiful
I'm f**king woman, I'm f**king beauty
We're f**king women, we're f**king beauty
YOU! ど面でも高所でモーション
YOU! Motion even at high places
膨大放送待つでしょん
Waiting for the massive broadcast
どうしたの？皆様待つでしょ
What's wrong? Everyone is waiting
無敵に緊張してる待つれど
Invincibly nervous, yet waiting
Look at this の録画でも
Even in the recording of 'Look at this'
解けない憂鬱もスマートでゴー
Go smart with the unsolvable melancholy
パンクしそうならぶちまけろ
If you're about to burst, pour it out
気持ちごちゃごちゃ! ワンショット!
Mixed feelings! One shot!
錠剤 液体 はっきりしない実体
Pill, liquid, an unclear entity
それは期待か？答えか？期待か？答えか？
Is it expectation? Or the answer? Expectation? Answer?
生きたい 動体 全てを君の期待に応え
Living thing, moving body, meeting all your expectations
砕いて 裂いて 巻いて 焚いて 吸って 吐いても
Crush it, tear it, roll it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it
燃して 炙っても 打っても 得れない快感
Burn it, roast it, shoot it, yet no pleasure gained
たまらず君様
Can't help it, my dear Lord
耳から体内に入る
Enters the body through the ears
名前も虫歯のおかず
The name is just a side dish for a cavity
ポイズン再生するたび 生き生き返る
Poison, coming back to life every time it plays
お前の価値観いじくり脱皮
Messing with your values, molting
Its alright groovy
クリーンする世界の中心
Cleaning the center of the world
嵌まっちまったら終身
If you get hooked, it's life imprisonment
刑務所の名は MUSIC
The name of the prison is MUSIC
高層ビルの谷間から海の向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to across the sea
Maesu-ru sex and drug and rock'n roll
調教済みの部下共は声上げろ
You trained subordinates, raise your voices
超越する sex and drug and rock'n roll
Transcending sex and drug and rock'n roll
遠の昔に外れたブレーキ
The brakes failed long ago
逆らえない本能
Instinct you can't resist
Crystal Meth も Purple Haze も
Crystal Meth and Purple Haze
ワセリンよりじょろう
Easier than Vaseline
睦むへしらでも crazy
Even if we're intimate, it's crazy
泰定と microphone ようこそ
Welcome to tranquility and the microphone
合法的なトビ方を心得よ
Learn the legal way to fly
高層ビルの谷間から海の向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to across the sea
Maesu-ru sex and drug and rock'n roll
調教済みの部下共は声上げろ
You trained subordinates, raise your voices
超越する sex and drug and rock'n roll
Transcending sex and drug and rock'n roll
疾風怒濤に外れたブレーキ　逆らえない本能
Brakes gone in a violent storm, an uncontrollable instinct
クリスタル・メスもパープル・ヘイズも出せぬ熱情
A passion that neither crystal meth nor Purple Haze can ignite
鳴っても平静　狂ってもクレイジー　Take to the micro
Calm even if it rings, crazy even if you go mad, take to the micro
ようこそ合法的トビ方を心得よう
Welcome, let's learn the legal way to fly high
巻いて抱いて吸って吐いて打って捨てて置かないぜ
Roll it, hold it, inhale it, exhale it, hit it, I won't leave it behind
酔っぱらって抱いて寄せて止めてよしてええ加減
Getting drunk, holding on, pulling closer, stop it, cut it out, that's enough
洒落てなくて小汚くて土臭くて品がないぜ
Not stylish, a bit messy, earthy, and lacking in elegance
いっぱいなの安家からはこれで飛ばなきゃ損ぜ
In a house full of people, it's a loss if you don't fly with this
巻いて抱いて吸って吐いて打って捨てて置かないぜ
Roll it, hold it, inhale it, exhale it, hit it, I won't leave it behind
酔っぱらって抱いて寄せて止めてよしてええ加減
Getting drunk, holding on, pulling closer, stop it, cut it out, that's enough
洒落てなくて小汚くて土臭くて品がないぜ
Not stylish, a bit messy, earthy, and lacking in elegance
段取り取っても出来たなら一気に飛んで舞い上がれ
Even if you make plans, once it's done, fly up and soar at once
山の頂から谷底から海の向こう
From the mountaintop, from the valley floor, to beyond the sea
毎度お騒がせします　ジャパロウ
Sorry for the constant disturbance, Japarou
超高速の無礼講　どいつもこいつも声上げろ
Super-speed free-for-all, everyone raise your voice
超常現象　接吻　ジャック・ア・ロー
Paranormal phenomenon, kiss, Jack-a-roe
疾風怒濤に外れたブレーキ　逆らえない本能
Brakes gone in a violent storm, an uncontrollable instinct
クリスタル・メスもパープル・ヘイズも出せぬ熱情
A passion that neither crystal meth nor Purple Haze can ignite
鳴っても平静　狂ってもクレイジー　Take to the micro
Calm even if it rings, crazy even if you go mad, take to the micro
ようこそ合法的トビ方を心得よう
Welcome, let's learn the legal way to fly high
ふぅ。みなさん、今日の楽しいライブ配信に来てくれて誠にありがとうございます。
Phew. Everyone, thank you so much for coming to today's fun live stream.
今日もラップしたいと思います。
I'd like to rap today too.
では、始めましょうか。
Well then, shall we begin?
Okay, motherfucker, the Reaper is back one more time
At the pinnacle of your pathetic little lives
Come and get me, motherfucker, start up the roast! / How're ya feeling? I'm the motherfucking holy ghost!
In my sights, shots fired, boom, and you're dead / Next thing you're in a motherfucking flowerbed, bitch!
Say your prayers, I'm the hunter, you're the prey / I'm the star of my life, every single day
Jokes aside, back at the house, how's it look? / I see you, no one's gonna buy this bitch out of the book!
Cutest all hell in a little bit of sense / A bit of pretense, looking all hell, no show dollars and cents
To the me-and-you, the queen sayonara / Cypher to the super-erratic, poise to tear your heart apart
At the same soul-killer of your dreams / If you go into my pocket, then I've proved the scene
It's like that if you take my advice / You'll be killed by what you don't know
But I'll say that I like so much more / So of the vibes to keep it, f**k you say so!
Gotta know ain't so good to let go / I am soul of me, sugoi dashi!
Gotta know ain't so good to let go / I am soul of me, amazing broth!
Live for my life till the end of the day / Shitsurei shimasuga, shinde kudasai!
Live for my life till the end of the day / Excuse my rudeness, but please die!
Kill 'em with the bass! / この世の事、多々楽し
Kill 'em with the bass! / So many things to enjoy in this world
See, bitch! / My life is so fucking kawaii!
See, bitch! / My life is so fucking cute!
いいね！ 死神先生 勝負よ!
Nice! Reaper-sensei, let's have a match!
Kill 'em with the bass! So we get 'em to stay, alright? / (YES!) 素敵なアサ!
Kill 'em with the bass! So we get 'em to stay, alright? / (YES!) A wonderful morning!
So let's go! / Death is what you want me, come on and up ya!
勝手にやってる自己肯定　犯罪じゃないから、BASE さよなら
Self-affirmation done on my own, since it's not a crime, so BASE sayonara
Ex-terminate 'em, it's human nature / はあちゃまのマイライフ 超楽しい!
Ex-terminate 'em, it's human nature / Haachama's my life is super fun!
私も! あなたも! 死ぬまで!
Me! You! Until the day we die!
申し訳ないです　やりすぎました / なんで敬語でラップしてたら　ちょっと変だ
I am so sorry, I went a bit too far / Rapping in polite Japanese is a bit strange, isn't it?
Don't you step back, better taste straight forward / Head the other way and hell slammin' on your keyboard
Go ahead and be sour, but I won't run / I'm a workaholic, just this lady gettin' shit done
Takin' souls, nuttin' in the super-size for one / But it's a mystery as dark as the day in the sun
Come on! / In and above, I will love above, I will love above for my own thing
If you wanna get round about for my own thing / Motherf**ker wants a nap in the party?
Gonna take a fast step into the party / Kill 'em, come on, mother, I'm at the party
I'm not gonna down, I'm not gonna down / Come on and and and and love for me
Even the top of some advise / You'll be killed by what you don't know
But you sound kind of nervous and I don't know what the words are / On the other side of the gap, f**k it say so!
Tell me now, what I'm supposed to do? / I am close to you, and daijoubu!
Tell me now, what I'm supposed to do? / I am close to you, and it's okay!
I am so with you, the queen of life / Go ahead and enjoy life, and shitsurei shimasuga, shinde kudasai!
I am so with you, the queen of life / Go ahead and enjoy life, and excuse my rudeness, but please die!
Kill 'em with the bass! / この世の事、多々楽し
Kill 'em with the bass! / So many things to enjoy in this world
See, bitch! / My life is so fucking kawaii!
See, bitch! / My life is so fucking cute!
いいね！ 死神先生 勝負よ!
Nice! Reaper-sensei, let's have a match!
Kill 'em with the bass! So we get 'em to stay, alright? / (YES!) 素敵なアサ!
Kill 'em with the bass! So we get 'em to stay, alright? / (YES!) A wonderful morning!
So let's go! / Death is what you want me, come on and up ya!
勝手にやってる自己肯定　犯罪じゃないから、BASE さよなら
Self-affirmation done on my own, since it's not a crime, so BASE sayonara
Ex-terminate 'em, it's human nature / はあちゃまのマイライフ 超楽しい!
Ex-terminate 'em, it's human nature / Haachama's my life is super fun!
私も! あなたも! 死ぬまで!
Me! You! Until the day we die!
もう一回！ Kill 'em with the bass! / この世の事、多々楽し
One more time! Kill 'em with the bass! / So many things to enjoy in this world
勝手にやってる自己肯定　犯罪じゃないから、BASE さよなら
Self-affirmation done on my own, since it's not a crime, so BASE sayonara
Ex-terminate 'em, it's human nature / はあちゃまのマイライフ 超楽しい!
Ex-terminate 'em, it's human nature / Haachama's my life is super fun!
私も! あなたも! 死ぬまで!
Me! You! Until the day we die!
これで万物に愛されただろ！
Now I'm loved by everything in creation, right?!
ははははは！
Hahahahaha!
今のはあちゃまは、最強！
The current Haachama is the strongest!
次はB A N、バンッ、つって。
Next is B-A-N, bang, just like that.
むっ、気づかれたか！
Hm, they noticed me!
だが！ 今のハアチャマは無敵！
But! Right now, Haachama is invincible!
かかってきな！
Come at me!
KARATE 作詞・作曲: Yuyoyuppe
KARATE Lyrics/Composition: Yuyoyuppe
セイヤ、セセセセイヤ
Seiya, se-se-se-seiya
ソイヤ、ソソソソイヤ
Soiya, so-so-so-soiya
涙こぼれても
Even if tears fall
立ち向かってゆこうぜ
Let's stand and face it
ひたすら セイヤ ソイヤ 戦うんだ
Just keep on Seiya Soiya, fighting
拳をもっと 心をもっと
More of our fists, more of our hearts
全部全部 研ぎ澄まして
Sharpening every single thing
まだまだ セイヤ ソイヤ 戦うんだ
Still Seiya Soiya, fighting
悲しくなって 立ち上がれなくなっても
Even if we get sad and can't stand up anymore
セイヤ、セセセセイヤ
Seiya, se-se-se-seiya
ソイヤ、ソソソソイヤ
Soiya, so-so-so-soiya
心 折れても
Even if our hearts break
立ち向かってゆこうぜ
Let's stand and face it
ひたすら セイヤ ソイヤ 戦うんだ
Just keep on Seiya Soiya, fighting
拳をもっと 心をもっと
More of our fists, more of our hearts
全部全部 研ぎ澄まして
Sharpening every single thing
ひたすら セイヤ ソイヤ 戦うんだ
Just keep on Seiya Soiya, fighting
拳をもっと 心をもっと
More of our fists, more of our hearts
全部全部 研ぎ澄まして
Sharpening every single thing
まだまだ セイヤ ソイヤ 戦うんだ
Still Seiya Soiya, fighting
悲しくなって 立ち上がれなくなっても
Even if we get sad and can't stand up anymore
走れー！
Run!
セイヤ ソイヤ 戦うんだ
Seiya Soiya, fighting
走れー！
Run!
全部全部 研ぎ澄まして
Sharpening every single thing
これでどうだ！
How's this!
やばい、この雰囲気...
Oh no, this atmosphere...
助けて...
Help me...
どうしよう...
What should I do...
誰か... 助けて...
Someone... please help me...
そうだ...
That's right...
私は一人じゃない...
I'm not alone...
ここまで一緒に頑張ってきた...
I have friends who have worked hard...
仲間がいるんだ！
together with me until now!
みんな！
Everyone!
助けてくれー！
Help me!
はあちゃまっちゃま〜！
Haachama-chama!
ワールドワイドな最強アイドル！
The worldwide strongest idol!
はあちゃまこと、赤井はあとです！
Haachama, also known as Akai Haato!
今日はスペシャルな内容で
Today I'd like to bring you
お送りしたいと思います！
some special content!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
YouTube テーマソング
YouTube Theme Song
作詞・作曲：HIKAKIN & SEIKIN
Lyrics/Composition: HIKAKIN & SEIKIN
YouTube YouTube
主役は君なのさ HEY!
The star is you, HEY!
今日は日曜日
Today is Sunday
外は雨降りだ
It's raining outside
何をしようか
What should I do?
そうだ YouTube 観よう
Oh, let's watch YouTube
24時間
24 hours a day
朝 昼 夜 でも
Morning, noon, or night
好きな時間に
At any time you like
好きな動画観よう
Watch any video you like
いつも夢見ていた
I always dreamed of a
スクリーンデビュー
Screen debut
今なら叶うさ
Now it can come true
夢諦めるな
Don't give up on your dreams
Let's Try Again!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ
The star is you
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
夢を掴め YouTube! HEY!
Grab your dreams, YouTube! HEY!
カメラ片手に
With a camera in hand
夜空見上げよう
Let's look up at the night sky
流星群だ
It's a meteor shower
すぐに動画撮ろう
Let's film it right away
君が見つけた
The beauty of the universe
宇宙の美しさ HEY!
that you found, HEY!
見せてあげよう
Let me show it
世界中の人へ
to the people all over the world
誰もが悩み不安
Everyone probably has
抱えているだろう
worries and anxieties
勇気を与えよう
Let's give them courage
僕らの動画で
with our videos
Let's Try Again!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ
The star is you
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
夢を掴め YouTube!
Grab your dreams, YouTube!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ HEY!
The star is you, HEY!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
夢を掴め YouTube! HEY!
Grab your dreams, YouTube! HEY!
YouTubeテーマソング
YouTube Theme Song
みんなー！ありがとなー！
Everyone! Thank you!
仲間たちのおかげで、チャンネルBANの危機を逃れられた！
Thanks to my friends, I escaped the crisis of a channel ban!
こっからは… そりあがれー！
From here on... let's cut loose!
万物も！万物も！
Everything! Everything!
みんなで盛り上がってけー！
Everyone, let's get hyped!
PERFECT HUMAN
作詞：RADIO FISH　作曲：JUVENILE
Lyrics: RADIO FISH / Composition: JUVENILE
彼は言った 世界は必ずしもみんな平等とは限らない
He said, the world isn't necessarily equal for everyone
彼は言った 世の中には絶対勝者と敗者が存在する
He said, in this world, there are absolute winners and losers
彼は言った その勝者の頂点が自分自身 Top of the world
He said, the pinnacle of those winners is himself, Top of the world
彼が法であり秩序保たれる すぐさまなくなる世界の不安
He is the law and order is maintained; immediately the world's anxiety fades
時は来た 彼こそ真の支配者
The time has come, he is the true ruler
彼の前にひざまずくのは敗者
Those who kneel before him are the losers
感謝の言葉 彼に乱射
Words of gratitude, fired rapidly at him
賢者 さあ かけろ 拍車
Sages, come on, spur him on
民共 崇める準備はいいか？
Commoners, are you ready to worship?
自分を高める運気欲しいか？
Do you want the luck to elevate yourselves?
さあみんな手を天にかかげ そして今こそ祈れ
Now everyone raise your hands to the sky, and now pray
恐れるな
Don't be afraid
おののくな
Don't tremble
吠えろ
Roar
声あげろ
Raise your voice
その血と
With that blood and
魂を
soul
今 ささげろ
offer it now
I'm a perfect human.
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
We live in Tokyo
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
I'm a perfect human.
We believe in Nakata
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
I'm a perfect human.
大地パッカーン 海もパッカーン 気取ってるモーゼとかいう奴もパッカーン
Earth cracks open, sea cracks open, even that Moses guy putting on airs cracks open
そんなに褒めるのやめてくれよ ペコペコすんよな おいナポレオン
Stop praising me so much; don't bow down, hey Napoleon
キングならそう 歴史くつがえす 彼こそすなわち Top of the world
If he's a king, he overturns history; he is namely Top of the world
A to the T to the S to the U to the H to the I to the K to the O
ありがたきこの名を呼んでみよう ATSUHIKO
Let's try calling this grateful name, ATSUHIKO
Say 天才！(天才！)
Say Genius! (Genius!)
まさに天才！(天才！)
Truly a genius! (Genius!)
Say 天才！(天才！)
Say Genius! (Genius!)
まさに天才！(天才！)
Truly a genius! (Genius!)
Say 天才！(天才！)
Say Genius! (Genius!)
もっともっと叫べ！
Scream more and more!
恐れるな
Don't be afraid
おののくな
Don't tremble
吠えろ
Roar
声あげろ
Raise your voice
その血と
With that blood and
魂を
soul
今 ささげろ
offer it now
I'm a perfect human.
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
We live in Tokyo
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
I'm a perfect human.
We believe in Nakata
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
I'm a perfect human.
na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta, na, ka, ta
万物に愛されちゃま計画
The Plan to be Loved by All Things
はあちゃまっちゃま～！
Haachamachama~!
ワールドワイドな最強アイドル、はあちゃまこと赤井はあとです！
The world-wide strongest idol, Haachama aka Akai Haato here!
みんなー！
Everyone!
はあちゃま爆誕祭2024に来てくれてありがとうー！
Thank you for coming to Haachama Birthday Festival 2024!
というわけで、はあちゃま爆誕しましたよー！
And so, Haachama has been born!
みんな、どうだったライブ？
Everyone, how was the live?
楽しめてるかなー？
Are you enjoying it?
ちょっと！はあとをどかして！
Hey! Move Haato away!
あれ？あれ聞こえて...
Huh? I can hear...
というわけで、SPはあとずです！
So, we are the SP Haatos!
みんな、かっこいいポーズしてる！
Everyone, they're doing cool poses!
SPはあとも爆誕しちゃいましたよー！
SP Haato has also been born!
セクシーなポーズしておりますが...
I'm doing some sexy poses, but...
ちょっと一緒に撮影とかしちゃう？
Want to take some photos together?
はあちゃまだってセクシーポーズできるんだからな！
Haachama can do sexy poses too, you know!
よいしょ... うーん...
Here we go... mmm...
どうや！
How's that!
なんだなんだ上から見てんだ？
What's this, you're looking down on me?
何上から見てんだよ、全く！
Why are you looking down on me, seriously!
ま、それはさておき。
Well, setting that aside.
今回、万物に愛されちゃま計画というわけでね...
This time, as part of the
"Loved by All Things Chama Project"...
ステージ、新しいステージを作ってもらいました！
I had a new stage made!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
うぉー！タランチュラもあるし、信号機とかもある！
Woah! There's a tarantula, and even traffic lights!
お、あれ？なんか... あれ？禁止テープみたいな...
Oh, what's that? Huh? Like some caution tape...
結構危ない感じ？
Does it feel pretty dangerous?
ちょっとそういう感じあるんじゃないの？
Isn't there a bit of that vibe?
そしてそして！
And also, and also!
もちろんグッズもあるよー！
Of course, there's merchandise too!
ほちゃー！
Ta-da!
赤井はあと誕生日記念グッズです！
It's Akai Haato birthday commemorative merchandise!
詳細はこちらー！
Here are the details!
まずは、HENTシャツ！
First up, the "HENT" shirt!
みかんさん描き下ろしの、ダークで悪い感じのはあちゃまがプリントされました！
It features a print of a dark and wicked
Haachama, newly illustrated by Mikan-san!
文字が書いてありますね。
There's some text written on it.
Everybody say HENTAI! って書いてあるよ！
It says "Everybody say HENTAI!"!
HENTAI! HENTAI!
あ、ちょっと変態ポーズしてる。
Oh, I'm doing a pervert pose.
HENTAI! HENTAI!
あれ、そうさい... ちょっとそんなTシャツ着て、あんた変態なんじゃないの？
Wait, wait... wearing a T-shirt like that,
aren't you a pervert?
全く。ぜひ着てね。次は、こちら！
Honestly. Please wear it. Next is this!
BAN缶バッジ！
The BAN Can Badge!
同じくみかんさん描き下ろしのTシャツのイラストが缶バッジに！
The same T-shirt illustration by Mikan-san
is now a can badge!
これは... BAN缶バッジ！
This is... the BAN Can Badge!
みんなもぜひこれを付けてBANされろ...
Everyone, please wear this and get banned...
BANされない、BANされない。なんでもないです。次は、こちら！
No, don't get banned, don't get banned.
Never mind. Next is this!
フロミーズボトル！
The Frommeese Bottle!
お風呂に入ってるはあちゃまのデザインが入ったウォーター...
A water bottle with a design of
Haachama in the bath...
すごい飲んでる、飲んでる！なんか爽やかに！飲ん... こんなワインを片手にみたいな感じでね、飲んじゃったりして。
Wow, she's drinking it, drinking it!
So refreshingly! Drinking... like holding a glass
of wine in one hand, you know, just drinking away.
はあちゃまのおフロ水で色んな栄養補給しちゃう？
Want to replenish your nutrients with
Haachama's bath water?
はあちゃまのおフロ水ウォーターボトル。ぜひとも手に入れてみてね。
Haachama's bath water bottle.
Please do get your hands on one.
次は... さささ、次はこちら！
Next is... right, right, next is this!
タランちゃまぬいぐるみ！
The Taran-chama plushie!
まさか！ムメイちゃんが配信で描いてくれたキャラクターがグッズ化しました！
No way! The character Mumei-chan drew
during a stream has been turned into merchandise!
イェーイ！ありがとう、ムメイちゃん！
Yay! Thank you, Mumei-chan!
タランちゃまの可愛いぬいぐるみだよ。
It's a cute Taran-chama plushie.
ぜひタランちゃまと一緒にお外を歩き回ってほしいな。
I'd love for you to walk around outside
with Taran-chama.
そして次、こちら！
And next, this!
シチュエーションボイス「お風呂でもそばにいて♡」ってタイトルですけど...
The situation voice "Be by my side even in
the bath ♡" is the title, but...
どうぞ！またこんな... ああ... さっぱりしちゃってる。
Here you go! Again, this... ah...
it's so refreshing.
どんな内容なのかは購入して聴いてみてね。
Please buy it to find out what the content is.
クレーム（苦情）は受け付けません！
Complaints will not be accepted!
次はこちら！誕生日記念フルセット！
Next is this! The Birthday Commemoration Full Set!
購入特典は直筆サイン入りブロマイドカード！
The purchase bonus is a bromide card with
a handwritten signature!
カッコいい！
So cool!
数量限定じゃないので、買ってくれたみんなに直筆サイン書くよ！
It's not limited in quantity, so I'll sign it
for everyone who buys it!
無制限で頑張るぞー！
I'll do my best without a limit!
ぜひともお買い求めよろしくお願いします。
Please do consider purchasing.
はーい！
Yes!
ではでは。そしてね、今日ライブやって参りましたけども。
Well then. Also, we've been doing the live today.
次もまだまだライブはあります... が！
There's still more live to come... but!
ライブが終わってからメンバーシップ限定でアンコールライブもやるので、みんな最後まで見てね！よろしく！
After the live ends, I'll be doing an encore
live exclusively for members, so everyone,
please watch until the end! Thank you!
みんな、見てほしいの！
Everyone, I want you to see this!
というわけで、新曲でまーす！
So, a new song is coming out!
（笑）さらっと告知しちゃったよ！
(Laughs) I just blurted out the announcement!
BAN RTA、この後歌うよ！
I'm singing BAN RTA right after this!
作詞作曲ははあちゃま、編曲、ハヤシベトモノリさんにお願いしました。
I wrote the lyrics and music, and Tomonori Hayashibe did the arrangement.
歌うよ！ありがとう！
I'm singing it! Thank you!
めちゃめちゃ最高に、最高になってるからぜひとも聞いてほしい！
It turned out absolutely amazing, so I really want you all to hear it!
ってか、この後歌う！
I mean, I'm singing it next!
この後、本日24時に配信開始！
It starts streaming today at 24:00!
というわけでね、いや、みんな、ありがとうございました。
So yeah, thank you everyone.
最後に、みんなに伝えたいことがあります。
Finally, there's something I want to tell you all.
聞いてください。
Please listen.
BAN RTA。
BAN RTA.
If you wanna it dive in
Nothing's gonna happen if you wait
Do you all like thrills?
Aren't you get bored with life?
Even I'm excited about falling
That figure is aesthetics
Would you rather choose a life of...
Peaceful or Stormy
There are times in life when you fall
But if you never fall, you won't climb",
You've said it's like an attraction
Don't be afraid to fall!
Gonna dive in!
BAN BAN BAN BAN BAN RTA
The straight and narrow path is not enough
Those words will make you the strongest
Chant it in your heart!
That's the magical word "HENTAI"
There are many kinds of tears
Painful or Pleasant
I think I'm going crazy
Isn't it happier?
There's sometimes we're hopeless
You can't climb without descending
If you're scared of falling
There's no up
No way I know my future
That's why focus on my feeling
I'm the best idol in the world
She said you are "HENTAI"
When we cross the red light, that's tight
No matter how ashamed we're, it's alright
Are you feeling spicy?
I see that you're horny
Then I will be sexy and lose my mind
Oh no! I can't stop my heart beating...
Now I'm gonna drive into shock!
I am crazy about...!
BAN BAN BAN BAN BAN RTA
Down down down down down together
I'm not afraid to bare my soul
We can be strong and never lonely
Can I chant that word?
NO WAY NO WAY!
Down down down down down together
I'm not afraid to bare my soul
We can be strong and never lonely
Don't you miss that word?
You can't say it yet
Everybody say...
No! Yeah!
Aren't you feeling excited?
Now that time has come
Everybody say "HENTAI"
このあと 21:05 MV公開!
MV release at 21:05 after this!